(this.webpackJsonppoc_convo_quiz=this.webpackJsonppoc_convo_quiz||[]).push([[0],Array(23).concat([function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family1.00419f3d.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family2.d1707663.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family3.6c9aeae1.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family4.bdbe423f.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family5.97b0ccb3.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family6.7dad0582.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family7.712c4b37.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family8.6705b6da.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family9.b87f6af6.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family10.7a5f15ac.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family11.7f07c48c.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/family12.091834e2.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food1.d0381a84.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food2.0028b8d5.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food3.83387cad.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food4.21b8d436.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food5.02047798.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food6.63a41e37.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food7.607b4a16.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food8.28b5c987.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food9.7cbe8e28.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food10.72217992.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food11.39ef3312.mp3"},function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/food12.5d66bf9b.mp3"},,,function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(74)},,,,,function(e,t,a){},,,,,,,,,,,,,,function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},,,,function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),o=a.n(n),s=a(18),i=a.n(s),r=(a(54),a(10)),l=a(19),u=a(20),c=a(48),d=a(47),m=a(21),f=a.n(m),p=a(11),b=a.n(p);a(68);var h=function(e){var t=e.isSubmitDisabled,a=e.submitAnswers,n=e.question;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"submit"},o.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){a(n)},disabled:t,id:"submit-answer",className:"myButton"},"Submit answer"))};var k=function(e){var t=e.history,a=e.nextQuestion,n=e.isNextDisabled,s=e.totalQuestions,i=e.question;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"next"},o.a.createElement("button",{disabled:n,id:"next",className:"myButton",onClick:function(){a(t,i,s)}},"Next"))};function y(e){var t=e.submitted,a=e.isSubmitDisabled,n=e.isNextDisabled,s=e.submitAnswers,i=e.change,r=e.match,l=e.history,u=e.nextQuestion,c=e.isIncorrect,d=e.correct,m=e.incorrect,p=e.questions,y=e.formRef,w=p.find((function(e){return e.id===r.params.questionId}));return o.a.createElement("section",{className:"question-screen"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"background-img",style:{gridArea:"header",border:"1px solid #ddd",padding:"30px"}},o.a.createElement("h3",{className:"poc-convo-title"},"POC Conversational Quiz"),o.a.createElement("header",{className:"question-info"},o.a.createElement("h3",null,o.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",w.id," of ",p.length)),o.a.createElement("h5",{className:"score"},o.a.createElement("span",null,d," correct, ",m," incorrect")),o.a.createElement("hr",null)),o.a.createElement("section",{className:"response-area"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},o.a.createElement("h3",null,w.questionText)),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"audio-player"},o.a.createElement(f.a,{src:w.audioLink,autoPlay:!0,controls:!0})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"response-box",onChange:function(e){i(e,w.blanks)}},o.a.createElement("form",{ref:y,autoComplete:"off"},b()(w.responseText))),o.a.createElement("div",{style:{marginTop:"10px"},className:"feedback"},!0===c&&b()(w.incorrectText),!1===c&&o.a.createElement("span",{className:"correct"},"Correct")),!t&&o.a.createElement(h,{question:w,submitAnswers:s,isSubmitDisabled:a}),o.a.createElement(k,{history:l,nextQuestion:u,isNextDisabled:n,totalQuestions:p.length,question:w}))))}a(69);var w=a(8);var v=function(){return o.a.createElement("section",{className:"start-end-screen"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"background-img",style:{gridArea:"header"}},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"start-title"},o.a.createElement("h2",null,"Conversational Quiz")),o.a.createElement("header",{className:"start-end-info"}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"center-button"},o.a.createElement(w.b,{id:"start-quiz",className:"myButton",to:"/question/1"},"Start Quiz"))))};a(73);var I=function(e){var t=e.correct,a=e.questionTotal,n=e.history,s=e.OnNewQuiz;return o.a.createElement("section",{className:"start-end-screen"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"background-img",style:{gridArea:"header"}},o.a.createElement("h2",null,"Conversational Quiz"),o.a.createElement("header",{className:"start-end-info"},o.a.createElement("div",null,t," of ",a," correct")," ",o.a.createElement("div",null,"\xa0\xa0",Math.floor(t/a*100),"%\xa0\xa0"),o.a.createElement("div",null,"Thanks for playing.")),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"center-button"},o.a.createElement("button",{id:"start-new-quiz",className:"myButton",onClick:function(){s(n)}},"Take the quiz again"))))},g=a(1),x=a(23),C=a.n(x),T=a(24),q=a.n(T),E=a(25),N=a.n(E),A=a(26),j=a.n(A),D=a(27),L=a.n(D),W=a(28),S=a.n(W),Q=a(29),M=a.n(Q),z=a(30),B=a.n(z),O=a(31),R=a.n(O),F=a(32),H=a.n(F),P=a(33),_=a.n(P),J=a(34),U=a.n(J),G=a(35),K=a.n(G),V=a(36),X=a.n(V),Y=a(37),Z=a.n(Y),$=a(38),ee=a.n($),te=a(39),ae=a.n(te),ne=a(40),oe=a.n(ne),se=a(41),ie=a.n(se),re=a(42),le=a.n(re),ue=a(43),ce=a.n(ue),de=a(44),me=a.n(de),fe=a(45),pe=a.n(fe),be=a(46),he=a.n(be),ke=[{id:"1",blanks:["blank1","blank2"],answers:"largeolder",incorrectText:'<span class="incorrect">Incorrect</span><div class="correct-answer">Correct Answer: I have a <u>large</u> family. There is my mother and father. Plus I have two <u>older</u> brothers and a sister.</div>',questionText:"Tell me something about your family.",responseText:'I have a <input autoComplete="off" id="blank1"> family. There is my mother and father. Plus I have two <input autoComplete="off" id="blank2"> brothers and a younger sister.',audioLink:C.a},{id:"2",blanks:["blank3","blank4","blank5","blank6"],answers:"smallunclescousinslarge",incorrectText:'<span class="incorrect">Incorrect</span><div class="correct-answer"> Correct Answer: I have a <u>small</u> family, just me and my mother and father. But my <u>uncles</u> and aunts and <u>cousins</u> live very nearby, so we seem like a <u>large</u> family.</div>',questionText:"Tell me something about your family.",responseText:'I have a <input autoComplete="off" id="blank3"> family, just me and my mother and father. But my <input autoComplete="off" id="blank4"> and aunts and <input autoComplete="off" id="blank5"> live very nearby, so we seem like a <input autoComplete="off" id="blank6"> family.',audioLink:q.a},{id:"3",blanks:["blank7","blank8","blank9","blank10"],answers:"wifeparentsrelativesclose",incorrectText:'<span class="incorrect">Incorrect</span><div class="correct-answer">Correct Answer: I recently got married, and my <u>wife</u> and I live alone in a small apartment. But her <u>parents</u> live nearby, and she has lots of <u>relatives</u>. She\u2019s very <u>close</u> to her family.</div>',questionText:"Tell me something about your family.",responseText:'I recently got married, and my <input autoComplete="off" id="blank7"> and I live alone in a small apartment. But her <input autoComplete="off" id="blank8"> live nearby, and she has lots of <input autoComplete="off" id="blank9">. She\u2019s very <input autoComplete="off" id="blank10"> to her family.',audioLink:N.a},{id:"4",blanks:["blank11","blank12","blank13"],answers:"twinquietdistant",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I have a <u>twin</u> brother. He is my only sibling, so ours is a <u>quiet</u> family. Most of our relatives live in another city, so we don't see them often. We have some <u>distant</u> cousins who live near us but I don't know them well.</div>",questionText:"Tell me something about your family.",responseText:"I have a <input autoComplete='off' id='blank11'> brother. He is my only sibling, so ours is a <input autoComplete='off' id='blank12'> family. Most of our relatives live in another city, so we don't see them often. We have some <input autoComplete='off' id='blank13'> cousins who live near us but I don't know them well.",audioLink:j.a},{id:"5",blanks:["blank14","blank15","blank16"],answers:"sportsvisitmeal",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: My brothers and sisters and I all enjoy <u>sports</u>, so we spend a lot ot time playing soccer and tennis together. Also, we usually <u>visit</u> our cousins every weekend and have a big <u>meal</u> with them.</div>",questionText:"What do you enjoy doing with your family?",responseText:"My brothers and sisters and I all enjoy <input autoComplete='off' id='blank14'>, so we spend a lot ot time playing soccer and tennis together. Also, we usually <input autoComplete='off' id='blank15'> our cousins every weekend and have a big <input autoComplete='off' id='blank16'> with them.",audioLink:L.a},{id:"6",blanks:["blank17","blank18","blank19","blank20"],answers:"readdiscussingopinionsstrange",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: We all like to <u>read</u> in our family, and we really enjoy <u>discussing</u> books together. We don't always have the same <u>opinions</u> about books, so we argue a lot. It may sound <u>strange</u>, but we think that's really fun.</div>",questionText:"What do you enjoy doing with your family?",responseText:"We all like to <input autoComplete='off' id='blank17'> in our family, and we really enjoy <input autoComplete='off' id='blank18'> books together. We don't always have the same <input autoComplete='off' id='blank19'> about books, so we argue a lot. It may sound <input autoComplete='off' id='blank20'>, but we think that's really fun.",audioLink:S.a},{id:"7",blanks:["blank21","blank22","blank23"],answers:"vacationrentinvite",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: We usually take a big family <u>vacation</u> every summer. We <u>rent</u> a big house at the beach and <u>invite</u> all our cousins to stay with us.</div>",questionText:"What do you enjoy doing with your family?",responseText:" We usually take a big family <input autoComplete='off' id='blank21'> every summer. We <input autoComplete='off' id='blank22'> a big house at the beach and <input autoComplete='off' id='blank23'> all our cousins to stay with us.",audioLink:M.a},{id:"8",blanks:["blank24","blank25","blank26","blank27"],answers:"busycookstalkrelaxing",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: Unfortunately, I am usually too <u>busy</u> to spend much time with my family because of my job. But I visit my parents when I can. My mother <u>cooks</u> a nice dinner for me, and we sit around and <u>talk</u> about things. It\u2019s quiet and <u>relaxing</u>.</div>",questionText:"What do you enjoy doing with your family?",responseText:"Unfortunately, I am usually too <input autoComplete='off' id='blank24'> to spend much time with my family because of my job. But I visit my parents when I can. My mother <input autoComplete='off' id='blank25'> a nice dinner for me, and we sit around and <input autoComplete='off' id='blank26'> about things. It\u2019s quiet and <input autoComplete='off' id='blank27'>.",audioLink:B.a},{id:"9",blanks:["blank28","blank29","blank30"],answers:"funshareinterests",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I like spending time with both family and friends. But to tell the truth, I have more <u>fun</u> with my friends. My friends and I <u>share</u> a lot of <u>interests</u>. That's why they're my friends.</div>",questionText:"Do you prefer spending time with your family or with friends?",responseText:"I like spending time with both family and friends. But to tell the truth, I have more <input autoComplete='off' id='blank28'> with my friends. My friends and I <input autoComplete='off' id='blank29'> a lot of <input autoComplete='off' id='blank30'>. That's why they're my friends.",audioLink:R.a},{id:"10",blanks:["blank31","blank32","blank33","blank34"],answers:"babyattentionhusbandfine",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I have a new <u>baby</u> so I don't have much time for friends. He takes most of my <u>attention</u>. For now, my friends are my <u>husband</u> and my son. That's <u>fine</u> with me.</div>",questionText:"Do you prefer spending time with your family or with friends?",responseText:"I have a new <input autoComplete='off' id='blank31'> so I don't have much time for friends. He takes most of my <input autoComplete='off' id='blank32'>. For now, my friends are my <input autoComplete='off' id='blank33'> and my son. That's <input autoComplete='off' id='blank34'> with me.",audioLink:H.a},{id:"11",blanks:["blank35","blank36"],answers:"activitiesin common",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I really enjoy spending time with my family. My brothers and sisters and I enjoy many of the same <u>activities</u>. We have a lot <u>in common</u>.</div>",questionText:"Do you prefer spending time with your family or with friends?",responseText:"I really enjoy spending time with my family. My brothers and sisters and I enjoy many of the same <input autoComplete='off' id='blank35'>. We have a lot <input autoComplete='off' id='blank36'>.",audioLink:_.a},{id:"12",blanks:["blank37","blank38","blank39"],answers:"groupslikeget along",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I have a lot of friends, and I enjoy spending time with them. We go out together in large <u>groups</u>. My friends are <u>like</u> a large family to me. I <u>get along</u> better with my friends than I do with my family.</div>",questionText:"Do you prefer spending time with your family or with friends?",responseText:"I have a lot of friends, and I enjoy spending time with them. We go out together in large <input autoComplete='off' id='blank37'>. My friends are <input autoComplete='off' id='blank38'> a large family to me. I <input autoComplete='off' id='blank39'> better with my friends than I do with my family.",audioLink:U.a},{id:"13",blanks:["blank40","blank41","blank42","blank43"],answers:"tryingdishesforeigndifferent",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I like <u>trying</u> all kinds of food. I especially like <u>dishes</u> from <u>foreign</u> countries. I always enjoy trying food that is new and <u>different</u>.</div>",questionText:"What kinds of food do you prefer to eat?",responseText:"I like <input autoComplete='off' id='blank40'> all kinds of food. I especially like <input autoComplete='off' id='blank41'> from <input autoComplete='off' id='blank42'> countries. I always enjoy trying food that is new and <input autoComplete='off' id='blank43'>.",audioLink:K.a},{id:"14",blanks:["blank44","blank45","blank46","blank47"],answers:"mealstraditionaldeliciouswell",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I like the <u>meals</u> my mother cooks. She cooks food that is <u>traditional</u> in our country. It's really <u>delicious</u>. Nobody cooks as <u>well</u> as my mother does.</div>",questionText:"What kinds of food do you prefer to eat?",responseText:"I like the <input autoComplete='off' id='blank44'> my mother cooks. She cooks food that is <input autoComplete='off' id='blank45'> in our country. It's really <input autoComplete='off' id='blank46'>. Nobody cooks as <input autoComplete='off' id='blank47'> as my mother does.",audioLink:X.a},{id:"15",blanks:["blank48","blank49","blank50","blank51"],answers:"vegetarianpreparedfreshfruit",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I am a <u>vegetarian</u>, so I never eat meat. I prefer food that's <u>prepared</u> with <u>fresh</u> vegetables. I eat a lot of <u>fruit</u>, too.</div>",questionText:"What kinds of food do you prefer to eat?",responseText:"I am a <input autoComplete='off' id='blank48'>, so I never eat meat. I prefer food that's <input autoComplete='off' id='blank49'> with <input autoComplete='off' id='blank50'> vegetables. I eat a lot of <input autoComplete='off' id='blank51'>, too.",audioLink:Z.a},{id:"16",blanks:["blank52","blank53","blank54","blank55","blank56"],answers:"chickenricedessertssweetvegetables",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I generally prefer to eat beef or <u>chicken</u> with <u>rice</u>. And I love <u>desserts</u>. I like anything that's <u>sweet</u>. I almost never eat <u>vegetables</u>.</div>",questionText:"What kinds of food do you prefer to eat?",responseText:"I generally prefer to eat beef or <input autoComplete='off' id='blank52'> with <input autoComplete='off' id='blank53'>. And I love <input autoComplete='off' id='blank54'>. I like anything that's <input autoComplete='off' id='blank55'>. I almost never eat <input autoComplete='off' id='blank56'>.",audioLink:ee.a},{id:"17",blanks:["blank57"],answers:"out",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I almost always eat at restaurants because I am <u>out</u> all day.</div>",questionText:"Do you usually eat at home or at restaurants?",responseText:"I almost always eat at restaurants because I am <input autoComplete='off' id='blank57'> all day.",audioLink:ae.a},{id:"18",blanks:["blank58","blank59","blank60"],answers:"breakfastdinnerweekends",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I always eat <u>breakfast</u> and <u>dinner</u> at home, and I eat lunch at home, too, when I can. But on <u>weekends</u>, I often go to restaurants with my friends.</div>",questionText:"Do you usually eat at home or at restaurants?",responseText:"I always eat <input autoComplete='off' id='blank58'> and <input autoComplete='off' id='blank59'> at home, and I eat lunch at home, too, when I can. But on <input autoComplete='off' id='blank60'>, I often go to restaurants with my friends.",audioLink:oe.a},{id:"19",blanks:["blank61","blank62","blank63"],answers:"expensivehavespecial occasion",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I usually eat at home because it's too <u>expensive</u> to eat at restaurants. I only <u>have</u> a meal at a restaurant when it's a <u>special occasion</u>, for example, someone\u2019s birthday.</div>",questionText:"Do you usually eat at home or at restaurants?",responseText:"I usually eat at home because it's too <input autoComplete='off' id='blank61'> to eat at restaurants. I only <input autoComplete='off' id='blank62'> a meal at a restaurant when it's a <input autoComplete='off' id='blank63'>, for example, someone\u2019s birthday.",audioLink:ie.a},{id:"20",blanks:["blank64","blank65","blank66"],answers:"convenientneighborhoodtastes",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I eat at home because it's more <u>convenient</u>. I have three children, so it's easier for us to eat at home. Also, there aren't many good restaurants in my <u>neighborhood</u>. I think the food we eat at home <u>tastes</u> better.</div>",questionText:"Do you usually eat at home or at restaurants?",responseText:"I eat at home because it's more <input autoComplete='off' id='blank64'>. I have three children, so it's easier for us to eat at home. Also, there aren't many good restaurants in my <input autoComplete='off' id='blank65'>. I think the food we eat at home <input autoComplete='off' id='blank66'> better.",audioLink:le.a},{id:"21",blanks:["blank67","blank68","blank69","blank70"],answers:"servescakessnackfrequently",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: My favorite restaurant is a small place near my house. It <u>serves</u> the most delicious <u>cakes</u>. It\u2019s a great place to go for an afternoon <u>snack</u>. I <u>frequently</u> meet my friends there.</div>",questionText:"What is your favorite restaurant?",responseText:"My favorite restaurant is a small place near my house. It <input autoComplete='off' id='blank67'> he most delicious <input autoComplete='off' id='blank68'>. It\u2019s a great place to go for an afternoon <input autoComplete='off' id='blank69'>. I <input autoComplete='off' id='blank70'> meet my friends there.",audioLink:ce.a},{id:"22",blanks:["blank71","blank72","blank73"],answers:"elegantbirthdayprices",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: There is a very <u>elegant</u> restaurant downtown that has French food. I had my <u>birthday</u> dinner there last year. The <u>prices</u> are high, so I can't go there very often, but I really like it.</div>",questionText:"What is your favorite restaurant?",responseText:"There is a very <input autoComplete='off' id='blank71'> restaurant downtown that has French food. I had my <input autoComplete='off' id='blank72'> dinner there last year. The <input autoComplete='off' id='blank73'> are high, so I can't go there very often, but I really like it.",audioLink:me.a},{id:"23",blanks:["blank74","blank75","blank76","blank77"],answers:"fast foodhamburgerquicklycheap",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: I like to go to a <u>fast food</u> restaurant near my school. I don't usually have a lot of time for lunch so it's a good place for me. I can get a <u>hamburger</u> or a sandwich there and eat it <u>quickly</u>. It\u2019s <u>cheap</u>, too.</div>",questionText:"What is your favorite restaurant?",responseText:"I like to go to a <input autoComplete='off' id='blank74'> restaurant near my school. I don't usually have a lot of time for lunch so it's a good place for me. I can get a <input autoComplete='off' id='blank75'> or a sandwich there and eat it <input autoComplete='off' id='blank76'>. It\u2019s <input autoComplete='off' id='blank77'>, too.",audioLink:pe.a},{id:"24",blanks:["blank78","blank79","blank80"],answers:"seafoodfishmenu",incorrectText:"<span class='incorrect'>Incorrect</span><div class='correct-answer'>Correct Answer: My favorite restaurant is a <u>seafood</u> restaurant near my house. I like it because I like <u>fish</u>. It has lots of other kinds of food on the <u>menu</u>, too.</div>",questionText:"What is your favorite restaurant?",responseText:"My favorite restaurant is a <input autoComplete='off' autoComplete='off' id='blank78'> restaurant near my house. I like it because I like <input autoComplete='off' autoComplete='off' id='blank79'>. It has lots of other kinds of food on the <input autoComplete='off' autoComplete='off' id='blank80'>, too.",audioLink:he.a}],ye=function(e){Object(c.a)(a,e);var t=Object(d.a)(a);function a(e){var o;return Object(l.a)(this,a),(o=t.call(this,e)).state={questionNum:1,submitDisabled:!0,submitted:!1,nextDisabled:!0,isIncorrect:"",correct:0,incorrect:0},o.handleOnChange=function(e,t){var a=e.target.value;o.setState(Object(r.a)({},e.target.id,a),(function(){t.every((function(e){return o.state[e]&&0!==o.state[e].trim().length}))?o.setState({submitDisabled:!1}):o.setState({submitDisabled:!0})}))},o.handleSubmit=function(e){var t="";e.blanks.forEach((function(e){t+=o.state[e].trim().toLowerCase(),o.setState(Object(r.a)({},e,""))})),t===e.answers?o.setState({isIncorrect:!1,correct:o.state.correct+1}):o.setState({isIncorrect:!0,incorrect:o.state.incorrect+1}),o.setState({submitted:!0,nextDisabled:!1})},o.handleNextQuestion=function(e,t,a){for(var n=0;n<t.blanks.length;n++)o.formRef.current[n].value="";o.state.questionNum===a?e.push("/EndQuiz"):o.setState({questionNum:o.state.questionNum+1,submitDisabled:!0,nextDisabled:!0,submitted:!1,isIncorrect:null},(function(){e.push("/question/".concat(o.state.questionNum))}))},o.handleNewQuiz=function(e){o.setState({questionNum:1,submitDisabled:!0,submitted:!1,nextDisabled:!0,isIncorrect:"",correct:0,incorrect:0}),e.push("/")},o.formRef=Object(n.createRef)(),o}return Object(u.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},o.a.createElement(g.c,null,o.a.createElement(g.a,{path:"/question/:questionId",render:function(t){var a=t.match,n=t.history;return o.a.createElement(y,{submitted:e.state.submitted,isSubmitDisabled:e.state.submitDisabled,isNextDisabled:e.state.nextDisabled,submitAnswers:function(t){e.handleSubmit(t)},change:e.handleOnChange,match:a,history:n,nextQuestion:e.handleNextQuestion,isIncorrect:e.state.isIncorrect,correct:e.state.correct,incorrect:e.state.incorrect,questions:ke,formRef:e.formRef})}}),o.a.createElement(g.a,{path:"/EndQuiz",render:function(t){var a=t.history;return o.a.createElement(I,{correct:e.state.correct,incorrect:e.state.incorrect,questionTotal:ke.length,history:a,OnNewQuiz:e.handleNewQuiz})}}),o.a.createElement(g.a,{path:"/"},o.a.createElement(v,null))))}}]),a}(o.a.Component);i.a.render(o.a.createElement(o.a.StrictMode,null,o.a.createElement(w.a,null,o.a.createElement(ye,null))),document.getElementById("root"))}]),[[49,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.01c7a959.chunk.js.map